Every life has a price
Sacrifice is a thriller, crime, mystery film directed by Peter A. Dowling.
Sacrifice is the story of consultant surgeon, Tora Hamilton, who moves with her husband, Duncan,
to the remote Shetland Islands, 100 miles off the north-east coast of Scotland.
Deep in the peat soil around her new home, Tora discovers the body of a young woman with
rune marks carved into her skin and a gaping hole where her heart once beat.
Ignoring warnings to leave well alone, Tora uncovers terrifying links to a legend
that might never have been confined to the pages of the story-books.
Dr. Tora Hamilton, played by Radha Mitchell.
Duncan Guthrie, played by Rupert Graves.
D.I. McKie, played by Ian McElhinney.
Richard Guthrie, played by David Robb.
Sgt. Dana Tulloch, played by Joanne Crawford.
Mr. Grey, played by Liam Carney.
Sacrifice is a 2016 American thriller film that was
written and directed by Peter A.
Dowling, and starred Radha Mitchell and Rupert Graves.
It was filmed in Ireland, in Shetland in the United Kingdom, and New York City.
The film is based on the book Sacrifice by Sharon Bolton.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, dead body, doctor.
The tone is mind_bending and thought_provoking and intense.